Guide to the Gorbachev Visit [videorecording]
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Gorbachev visit [videorecording]
1990
V0089
Stanford Instructional Television Network
1.5 Linear feet
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Scope and Contents
Tape of Mikhail Gorbachev's visit to Stanford University on June 4, 1990. VHS dub of unedited line cut.
Access Terms
Freedman, Estelle B., 1947-; Gorbachev, Mikhail Sergeevich, 1931-.; Kennedy, Donald, 1931-; Mosher, Clelia Duel, 1863-1940; Stanford University. Stanford Instructional Television Network.; Gorbachev, Mikhail; Kennedy, Donald.; Stanford University; Videorecordings.; Women--History.--United States; Women--Social conditions.--United States
Collection Contents
- Video (Box 1)
  - Soviet Survey(tape 10), 1990 May 25; 0 (Box 1)
  - Don Kennedy interview in Quad (tape 11), 1990 Jun 12; 0 (Box 1)
  - Wattis Rm. meeting with faculty, 1990 Jun 4; 1 videotape(s) (MII) (Box 1)
  - Program Feed Tape #0 (tape 12), 1990 Jun 4; 1 videotape(s) (MII) (Box 1)
  - Program Feed Tape #1 (tape 14), 1990 Jun 4; 1 videotape(s) (MII) (Box 1)
  - Program Feed Tape #2 (tape 15), 1990 Jun 4; 1 videotape(s) (MII) (Box 1)
  - Program Feed Tape #3 (tape 16), 1990 Jun 4; 1 videotape(s) (MII) (Box 1)
  - Program Feed Tape #4 (tape 17), 1990 Jun 4; 1 videotape(s) (MII) (Box 1)
  - VTR 1, Tape 1 of 3(tape 18), 1990 Jun 4; 1 videotape(s) (MII) (Box 2)
  - VTR 1, Tape 2 of 3 (tape 19), 1990 Jun 4; 1 videotape(s) (MII) (Box 2)
  - VTR 1, Tape 3 of 3 (tape 20), 1990 Jun 4; 1 videotape(s) (MII) (Box 2)
  - VTR 2, Tape 3 of 3, 1990 Jun 4; 1 videotape(s) (MII) (Box 2)
  - VTR 3, Reel 1 of 2 (tape 26), 1990 Jun 4; 1 videotape(s) (MII) (Box 2)
  - VTR 3, Tape 2 of 2 (tape 24), 1990 Jun 4; 1 videotape(s) (MII) (Box 2)
  - VTR 3, Tape 3 (tape 27), 1990 Jun 4; 1 videotape(s) (MII) (Box 2)
  - VTR 4, Tape 1 of 2 (tape 21), 1990 Jun 4; 1 videotape(s) (MII) (Box 3)
  - VTR 4, Tape 2 of 2 (tape 22), 1990 Jun 4; 1 videotape(s) (MII) (Box 3)
  - VTR 4, Tape 3(tape 28), 1990 Jun 4; 1 videotape(s) (MII) (Box 3)
  - VTR 5, Tape 1 of 2 (tape 25), 1990 Jun 4; 1 videotape(s) (MII) (Box 3)
  - VTR 5, Tape 2 of 2 (tape 23), 1990 Jun 4; 1 videotape(s) (MII) (Box 3)
  - VTR 5, Tape 3 (tape 29), 1990 Jun 4; 1 videotape(s) (MII) (Box 3)